The magic happens when you're up there
and everything's going great for you and
you can tell everything's going great
for the audience and you have this
symbiotic electrical relationship where
you're all in this groove together and
you're all sort of in suspended
animation for a while where you leave
the world outside and all of a sudden
we're all in this fantasy world that we
create that we're all living in for this
hour and a half and when that happens
when the whole world is sort of shuts
down and you're in this make-believe
world that all of a sudden becomes the
real world that you're in for an hour
and a half two hours where nothing else
exist except for that world then you're
in a movie.
Then you're in this alternate universe
that there's nothing but joy.